{
    "subject": "resource/Nina_Veselova",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Realism_(arts)",
    "human_readable": "Nina Veselova was associated with Realism (arts).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9483567476272583,
            "question": "Who were some prominent artists associated with Realism besides Nina Veselova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9359338879585266,
            "question": "What artistic movement was Nina Veselova associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9352058172225952,
            "question": "Are there any specific artworks by Nina Veselova that exemplify her connection to Realism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.77500319480896,
            "question": "How is Nina Veselova's work remembered within the context of the Realism movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5367223024368286,
            "question": "Nina Veselova's work is characterized by which style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5216670036315918,
            "question": "What art period did Realism belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3257301151752472,
            "question": "Can you name some key characteristics of Realism in art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28114816546440125,
            "question": "How did Realism differ from other art movements popular during the same time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2730286419391632,
            "question": "What impact did Realism have on the development of subsequent art movements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25211015343666077,
            "question": "What themes are commonly explored in Realistic artwork?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nina Veselova was associated with Realism (arts).",
            "html": "dbpedia_8611_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Realism have on the development of subsequent art movements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8611_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Realism differ from other art movements popular during the same time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8611_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some key characteristics of Realism in art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8611_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8611_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe text explicitly states that Nina Veselova was a \"Socialist realism painter\".  Since Socialist Realism is a form of Realism, the statement is supported. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Nina Veselova's artistic style and genre, which includes socialist realism. This indicates that she was indeed associated with the art movement of Realism (arts)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Nina Veselova is a \"Socialist realism painter,\" which supports the statement that she was associated with Realism in the arts. Socialist realism is a form of social and political realism that originated in the Soviet Union and was later adopted by other socialist states."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}